Guide to the Gay Men's Health Crisis records
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series VII. Education Department, 1982-1998, n.d.; 76.75 boxes
  - VII. C. AIDS Professional Education Program (APEP), 1982-1995; 15.5 boxes
    - VII. C. 2. Project Director Files, 1983-1992, n.d.
      - AIDS Institute, 1986-1987 (Box 163, Folder 7)
      - Alcoholism, 1987-1988 (Box 163, Folder 8)
      - Assessments, 1985-1990 (Box 163, Folder 9)
      - Bibliographies, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 10)
      - Brooklyn Psychiatric Centers, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 11)
      - Bureau of Mental Retardation and Development Disabilities, 1988-1989 (Box 163, Folder 12)
      - Charts and diagrams, 1987, n.d. (Box 163, Folder 13)
      - Child Welfare League, 1987-1988 (Box 163, Folder 14)
      - Chinese language materials, undated (Box 163, Folder 15)
      - Committee for AIDS Funding, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 16)
      - Comprehensive Care Program, 1990 (Box 163, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 1988, 1991 (Box 163, Folder 18)
      - Creole language materials, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 19)
      - Dartmouth College, Responsible AIDS Information at Dartmouth (RAID), 1988-1989 (Box 163, Folder 20)
      - Education goals, 1988 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - Evaluations, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 2)
      - Glossaries, 1990, n.d. (Box 164, Folder 3)
      - Gouverneur Hospital AIDS Assessment, 1989 (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - Greater New York Blood Program, 1986-1987 (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - HIV/Genetic Counseling, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - HIV and Women, 1988 (Box 164, Folder 7)
      - Jewish Child Care Association, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 8)
      - Levels of service, 1986-1992 (Box 164, Folder 9-12)
      - Lower Manhattan AIDS Task Force, 1989 (Box 164, Folder 13)
      - Memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box 164, Folder 14-15)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center
        - General, 1987-1988 (Box 165, Folder 1)
        - Evaluation aggregates, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 2)
        - Original proposal, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 3)
        - Status reports (Box 165, Folder 4-7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 165, Folder 8)
      - Mission statement, 1986-1987 (Box 165, Folder 9)
      - Moynihan, Sister Rosemary, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 10)
      - National Institute of Mental Health Peer Review, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 11)
      - New York City
        - AIDS resources, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 12)
        - AIDS Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 165, Folder 13)
        - Department of Mental Health, 1985-1989 (Box 165, Folder 14-16)
        - Politics, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 17)
      - New York State Five Year Inter-Agency AIDS Plan, 1990 (Box 166, Folder 1)
      - North Central Bronx, 1988-1989 (Box 166, Folder 2)
      - Notes, 1986? (Box 166, Folder 3)
      - Public Health Service Education at Columbia Presbyterian Medical Center, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 4)
      - Participating hospitals, 1986? (Box 166, Folder 5)
      - Research Press, 1987-1988 (Box 166, Folder 6)
      - Richardson, Susan, topical files
        - A-U, 1986-1991, n.d. (Box 166, Folder 7-16)
        - U-Y, 1987-1989 (Box 167, Folder 1-3)
      - St. Luke's\Roosevelt Hospital Center, 1987 (Box 167, Folder 4)
      - Sex Information and Education Council of the U.S. (SIECUS)
        - General, 1989 (Box 167, Folder 5)
        - Training, 1988 (Box 167, Folder 6)
      - Shernoff, Michael, undated (Box 167, Folder 7)
      - Staff meetings, 1988 (Box 167, Folder 8)
      - Staten Island, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 9)
      - Thank yous, 1991 (Box 167, Folder 10)
      - Training aggregates, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 11)
      - Training ARRIVE, 1991 (Box 167, Folder 12)
      - University of Illinois, 1987 (Box 167, Folder 13)
      - Victim Services, 1986? (Box 167, Folder 14)
      - Volunteer materials, 1983-1989 (Box 167, Folder 15)
      - Volunteer training, 1988 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - VII. C. 3. Trainings, 1986-1992
      - Addabbo-Altro, 1987-1991 (Box 167, Folder 17)
      - American Red Cross, 1990-1992 (Box 168, Folder 1)
      - Amico-Astor, 1987, 1991 (Box 168, Folder 2)
      - Bedford-BRC, 1990-1991 (Box 168, Folder 3)
      - Bridge-Bronx, 1987-1991 (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - Brooklyn, 1987-1991 (Box 168, Folder 5)
      - Catholic Charities, 1986, 1989-1991 (Box 168, Folder 6)
      - Center for Children and Families, 1991 (Box 168, Folder 7)
      - Child Welfare Administration, 1991 (Box 168, Folder 8)
      - City-Community Access, 1987, 1990-1991 (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - Community Counseling-Community Support, 1987-1991 (Box 168, Folder 10)
      - Coney-Creedmoor, 1986-1991 (Box 168, Folder 11)
      - Crotona-Dennelisse, 1987, 1991 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - East-Elmhurst Alcoholism, 1987-1991 (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - Elmhurst Department of Psychiatry, 1991 (Box 169, Folder 3)
      - Encore-Enter, 1987-1991 (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Federation Employment and Guidance Services, 1989-1991 (Box 169, Folder 5-7)
      - Fordham-Goodwill, 1987-1991 (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Gouverneur Hospital, 1988-1991 (Box 169, Folder 9-10)
      - Greenwich House, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - Guild-Harlem, 1986, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - Henry-Institute, 1987-1988, 1991 (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - International Center for the Disabled, 1988-1992 (Box 170, Folder 4-5)
      - Inwood-Jamaica, 1989-1991 (Box 170, Folder 6)
      - JBFC, 1986 (Box 170, Folder 7-8)
      - Jewish Child Care Association of New York
        - General, 1986-1987 (Box 170, Folder 9)
        - Brooklyn, Flatbush, 1988-1991 (Box 170, Folder 10)
        - Manhattan, 1986-1991 (Box 170, Folder 11-12)
        - North Brooklyn, Havemeyer, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 1)
        - Pleasantville, 1986, 1989-1991 (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Jewish Board-Jewish Guild, 1986-1988, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - Lexington-Manhattan Borough, 1987, 1990-1991 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - Manhattan Bowery Corporation, 1990-1991 (Box 171, Folder 5-6)
      - Manhattan Psychiatric Center, 1987, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 7)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1986-1990 (Box 171, Folder 8-9)
      - Mental-Montefiore, 1988-1991 (Box 171, Folder 10)
      - New Hope-New York City Criminal, 1987, 1990-1991 (Box 171, Folder 11)
      - New York City Department of Mental Health
        - Brooklyn-Children's, 1987-1990 (Box 171, Folder 12)
        - Community-Fordham, 1986, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 1)
        - Division of AIDS Services, 1990-1991 (Box 172, Folder 2)
        - Forensic-Task, 1986-1988 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - New York Psychotherapy-New York Society, 1987, 1991 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - New York State
        - Division of Alcoholism, 1989-1991 (Box 172, Folder 5)
        - Division of Human Rights, 1989-1991 (Box 172, Folder 6)
        - Division of Substance-Northside, 1987-1991 (Box 172, Folder 7)
      - Postgraduate-Pride, 1987, 1990-1991 (Box 172, Folder 8)
      - Professional Service Centers for the Handicapped
        - College Point, 1988-1991 (Box 173, Folder 1)
        - Horizon-OMNI III, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - Queens Child-Queens Hospital, 1987-1991 (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - Regional-Rockaway, 1986-1991 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Rose-Ryan, 1988-1991 (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - St. Barnabas Hospital, 1990-1991 (Box 173, Folder 6)
      - St. John-St. Luke, 1986, 1990-1991 (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - St. Vincent's Hospital
        - Alcohol Treatment Program, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 8)
        - North Richmond-Services, 1986-1991 (Box 173, Folder 9)
      - Settlement-Sex Information and Education Council of the U.S. (SIECUS), 1988, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 10)
      - Soundview Throgs Neck, 1986, 1989-1991 (Box 173, Folder 11-12)
      - South-Sprout, 1986-1987, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 13)
      - Staten Island AIDS-Staten Island Mental, 1986-1991 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Staten Island Teen-Steinway, 1989-1991 (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Transitional Services for New York, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - University-Very, 1987-1990 (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Victim Service Agency Project Safe, 1988-1991 (Box 174, Folder 5-6)
      - Victim Service Agency Traveller's Aid-Visiting, 1988-1991 (Box 174, Folder 7)
      - Volunteers of America, 1986-1991 (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Washington-Weston, 1986, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 9)
      - Women-Woodhull, 1987, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - Young-Youth, 1987-1991 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - VII. D. Community Health Education Services (CHES), 1982-1992, 1997; 14.25 boxes
    The Community Health Education Services (CHES) division of the Education Department was responsible for delivering AIDS information to the public via information tables, direct mail and telephone campaigns, as well as connecting with underserved communities. CHES accomplished these goals through a series of programs and initiatives: the Community Support Network, People of Color AIDS Prevention program, the Speakers' Bureau, and the distribution of pamphlets though tabling events.
    The Community Support Network (CSN) began in 1982 and maintained the distribution and collection of donation cans and literature at gay establishments, mostly bars and bathhouses. By 1988, more than 300 establishments in New York City participated in CSN.
    The People of Color AIDS Prevention (POC) program conducted outreach to gay and bisexual men of minority communities, mainly Blacks and Latinos. POC adapted its literature for these communities, created focus groups and advisory panels made up of members of the communities. Programs targeted at these communities included What's in it 4 Me?, a workshop by and for gay black men and Noche de Ronda ,a safe sex play in Spanish.
    The Speakers' Bureau was staffed by volunteers who gave presentations on HIV/AIDS and safe sex, their personal experiences with AIDS, homophobia and AIDS, and women and AIDS. These presentations were free and held at community centers, churches, schools, anywhere groups of people gathered. Tabling was another early program of GMHC. Volunteers distributed literature and were stationed at information tables throughout New York City in high traffic areas, especially ones with large populations of gay men. The service expanded to tables scheduled for street fairs, conferences, and health fairs.
    This subseries contains memoranda, reports, correspondence, and other material related to the Community Health Education Services division of the Education Department. The subseries is divided into eight sub-subseries: the Administrative Files of the department, the files of the Assistant Coordinator, the Assistant Director, and the Coordinator, the Community Support Network (CSN), the People of Color AIDS Prevention program, the Speakers' Bureau, and the Tabling initiative. Included here are information sheets on CSN establishments; statistical reports listing numbers and locations of literature and condoms distributed; assessments of outreach tables; plans for expansions of the division; the log of the Volunteer Manager which contains daily entries describing volunteer interviews, work done by volunteers, and other events of the day; memoranda on planned bar interventions and zaps; correspondence with organizations requesting Speakers' Bureau presentations; and reports on these events.
    - VII. D. 1. Administrative Files, 1986-1987
      - CHP Q & A, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - Follow-up calls to outreach letters, 1986-1987 (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - General assessment tabling evaluation forms, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - Mailings, 1986-1987 (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - Minority outreach, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 7)
      - National Council of the Churches of Christ/Division of Church and Society (NCC/DCS) Task Force on AIDS, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - Notes on video production, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 9)
      - Plans, 1986-1987 (Box 175, Folder 10)
      - Protocol, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 11)
      - Staff meetings, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 12)
      - Tabling assessment forms, 1986-1987 (Box 175, Folder 13-18)
      - Weekend tabling worksheets, 1986 (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - VII. D. 2. Assistant Coordinator Files, 1988-1992
      - Building on Diversity, 1990-1991 (Box 175, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 176, Folder 1-4)
      - Literature Review Project, 1990 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda, 1989-1991 (Box 176, Folder 6-10)
      - New Jersey Women and AIDS, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 11)
      - New York City Department of Health information and brochures, 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 12)
      - Other agency AIDS information, 1991 (Box 176, Folder 13)
      - Outreach Services reports, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 14)
      - People of Color AIDS Network, 1990? (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - Presentation materials, 1991 (Box 177, Folder 2)
      - Program planning, 1989-1991 (Box 177, Folder 3)
      - Staff Caucus, 1989-1990 (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Statistics
        - CHES, 1991-1992 (Box 177, Folder 5)
        - Speakers Bureau, 1992 (Box 177, Folder 6)
      - Tabling procedures, 1991 (Box 177, Folder 7)
      - Volunteer training notes, 1990 (Box 177, Folder 8)
      - Work plans, 1989-1990 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - VII. D. 3. Assistant Director File, 1987-1992
      - AIDS Preventive Health, 1987-1989 (Box 177, Folder 10)
      - Bathhouses, 1990 (Box 177, Folder 11)
      - Black outreach, 1988-1990 (Box 177, Folder 12-13)
      - Chemical use training, 1992 (Box 177, Folder 14)
      - Community Support Network, 1988-1990 (Box 177, Folder 15)
      - Condom study, 1989 (Box 177, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - Educational resources planning, 1990 (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Fire Island, 1990 (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - Health Education Week awards, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - House programs, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 5)
      - Hunter College, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 6)
      - La Escuelita, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 7)
      - Latino outreach, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 8)
      - Loveboat, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 9)
      - Mama Doesn't Know! production, 1989 (Box 178, Folder 10)
      - Marketing survey, 1989 (Box 178, Folder 11)
      - Memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 12)
      - Men + Men study, 1989 (Box 178, Folder 13)
      - New proposals guidelines and timeline, 1990 (Box 178, Folder 14)
      - New York City Department of Health
        - Adolescents
          - Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 178, Folder 15)
          - Proposal performance, 1990 (Box 178, Folder 16)
          - Proposal video, 1990 (Box 178, Folder 17)
        - Contract and GMHC guidelines, 1989-1991 (Box 178, Folder 18)
        - Guidelines, 1991-1992 (Box 178, Folder 19)
        - Monthly reports, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 20)
      - People of Color memoranda, 1990 (Box 179, Folder 1)
      - Prevention Planning
        - Day I, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 2)
        - Day II, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 3)
        - Day III, 1990 (Box 179, Folder 4)
        - Work group campaign, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - Prevention program reports, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 6)
      - Prevention programs, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 7)
      - Prevention Workgroup
        - Cross cultural, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 8)
        - Safer Sex, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 9)
        - Volunteers, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 10)
      - Preventive Health Seminars, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 11)
      - Program planning
        - Plays for Living, 1992 (Box 179, Folder 12)
        - Speakers Bureau, 1990 (Box 179, Folder 13)
      - Program plans, 1992 (Box 179, Folder 14)
      - Real People, 1990 (Box 179, Folder 15)
      - Reinfeld, Maggie, memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 16)
      - Safer Sex
        - Forum, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 17)
        - Videos, 1989? (Box 179, Folder 18)
      - Santa Cruz AIDS Project, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 19)
      - Speakers Bureau
        - General, 1988-1990 (Box 179, Folder 20)
        - HIV 101, 1991? (Box 179, Folder 21)
        - Meeting, 1992 (Box 179, Folder 22)
        - Report, 1992 (Box 179, Folder 23)
      - Statistical reports, 1991-1992 (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Tabling, 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Talking With Your Kids About AIDS outline, 1992 (Box 180, Folder 3)
      - U Men, U Sweat party, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Video/publications distribution, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Volunteers
        - General, 1986-1989 (Box 180, Folder 6)
        - Black outreach, 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 7)
        - Prevention, 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 8)
        - Training, 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - VII. D. 4 Coordinator Files, 1982-1997
      - 1987 National Lesbian & Gay Health Conference abstract (Box 180, Folder 10)
      - Bloom, Lenny, 1986 (Box 180, Folder 11)
      - Community Health Projects, 1986-1987 (Box 180, Folder 12)
      - Community Involvement Committee, 1985 (Box 180, Folder 13)
      - Complaints, 1986 (Box 180, Folder 14)
      - Congressional letters, 1986 (Box 180, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1987, 1990-1992, 1995 (Box 180, Folder 16-18)
      - Cultural sensitivity, 1986 (Box 180, Folder 19)
      - Deaf AIDS Project, 1991-1992 (Box 180, Folder 20)
      - Field evaluation instruments, 1988? (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Fire Island project, 1990-1991 (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - HIV guidelines, 1986 (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Hotline protocol
        - General, 1988? (Box 181, Folder 4)
        - Original Hotline 101, 1982? (Box 181, Folder 5)
        - Revision, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 6)
        - Six month plan, 1986 (Box 181, Folder 7)
        - Staff presentation, 1986-1987 (Box 181, Folder 8)
        - Training, 1988 (Box 181, Folder 9)
      - Latino-Hispanic outreach information, 1990 (Box 181, Folder 10)
      - Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Caucus, 1990-1991 (Box 181, Folder 11)
      - Lesbian information, 1991 (Box 181, Folder 12)
      - Lesbian workshop, 1991? (Box 181, Folder 13)
      - Literature rack lists, 1991-1992 (Box 181, Folder 14)
      - Media training, 1986 (Box 181, Folder 15)
      - Meetings
        - General staff, 1991-1992 (Box 181, Folder 16)
        - Education Department, 1987, 1991-1992, 1995-1996 (Box 181, Folder 17)
        - Notes with Frank Carson, 1991-1992 (Box 181, Folder 18)
      - Memoranda
        - In
          - General, 1986-1987, 1992 (Box 181, Folder 19-20)
          - Barna, Joe, 1990-1992 (Box 182, Folder 1)
          - Carson, Frank, 1991-1992 (Box 182, Folder 2)
          - Hinojos, Ernesto, 1992 (Box 182, Folder 3)
          - Klein, Richard, 1989-1992 (Box 182, Folder 4)
          - Resources, 1991-1992 (Box 182, Folder 5)
          - Sweeney, Timothy J., 1991-1992 (Box 182, Folder 6)
        - Out, 1992 (Box 182, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 182, Folder 8)
      - National Council of the Churches of Christ, 1986-1987 (Box 182, Folder 9)
      - Networking, 1991 (Box 182, Folder 10)
      - New Hotline data/corrections, 1986 (Box 182, Folder 11)
      - New York City Lesbian Health Fair, 1997 (Box 182, Folder 12)
      - New York State, 1987 (Box 182, Folder 13)
      - Outreach meetings, 1988 (Box 182, Folder 14)
      - Position papers, 1991 (Box 182, Folder 15)
      - Project Inform, 1986 (Box 182, Folder 16)
      - Reality women's condoms, 1990 (Box 182, Folder 17)
      - St. John the Divine service, 1987 (Box 182, Folder 18)
      - Speakers Bureau
        - Prisons, 1990-1991 (Box 182, Folder 19)
        - Volunteer meeting, 1992 (Box 182, Folder 20)
      - Tabling project, 1990 (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Unit meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 183, Folder 2)
      - Volunteers
        - Manager log, 1985-1986 (Box 183, Folder 3)
        - Manual, 1986 (Box 183, Folder 4)
        - Position descriptions, 1990 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - Volunteerism (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - Women and HIV/AIDS, 1989-1990 (Box 183, Folder 7)
      - Women's Education Services workgroup, 1991 (Box 183, Folder 8)
      - Work plans, 1992 (Box 183, Folder 9)
      - YMCA, 1987 (Box 183, Folder 10)
      - Youth Services workgroup, 1992 (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - VII. D. 5. Community Support Network, 1982-1987
      - Contribution cans and literature distribution, 1982-1984 (Box 183, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 183, Folder 13)
      - Establishment membership information, 1986? (Box 183, Folder 14)
      - Health fairs, 1985-1987 (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - VII. D. 6. People of Color AIDS Prevention, 1988-1992, 1997
      - VII. D. 6. a. Assistant Coordinator Files, 1988-1992
        - Bar interventions, 1991 (Box 183, Folder 16)
        - Bar Zaps, 1991 (Box 183, Folder 17)
        - Black Advisory Panel, 1988-1990 (Box 184, Folder 1-2)
        - Brochures, 1990, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 3)
        - Carta volunteers, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 4)
        - Clinical trials, 1990-1991 (Box 184, Folder 5)
        - Clinical trials training, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 6)
        - Education volunteers, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 7)
        - Entendidos, 1989 (Box 184, Folder 8)
        - Entrenamiento, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 9)
        - Hispanic AIDS Forum, 1990-1991 (Box 184, Folder 10-11)
        - Intake questionnaire Spanish translation, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 12)
        - Interventions, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 13)
        - Just Wear It, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 14)
        - La Condonera, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 15)
        - Latino Advisory Panel, 1988-1990 (Box 184, Folder 16)
        - Latino organizations, 1990-1991 (Box 184, Folder 17)
        - Latino programs, 1989-1991 (Box 184, Folder 18)
        - Latino volunteers, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 19)
        - Letters in, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 20)
        - The Loveboat, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 1)
        - Memoranda, 1990-1992 (Box 185, Folder 2)
        - Men Of Color against AIDS (MOCA) questionnaire, 1990 (Box 185, Folder 3)
        - Noche de Ronda, 1991-1992 (Box 185, Folder 4-5)
        - People of Color AIDS Prevention Program, 1990 (Box 185, Folder 6)
        - People of Color Resource Committee, 1992 (Box 185, Folder 7)
        - Prevention, 1992 (Box 185, Folder 8)
        - Programs
          - Development, 1989-1990 (Box 185, Folder 9)
          - Reviews, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 10)
          - Timelines and descriptions, 1990 (Box 185, Folder 11)
        - Spanish Language Print Review Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 185, Folder 12)
        - Spanish training, 1992 (Box 185, Folder 13)
      - VII. D. 6. b. Coordinator Files, 1988-1992, 1997
        - AIDS and the Latino Man, 1991? (Box 185, Folder 14)
        - Bar/club outreach, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 15)
        - Focus Group for Hispanic/Latino Men with HIV, 1991? (Box 185, Folder 16)
        - Gay Pride Parade, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 17)
        - Hispanics and AIDS, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 18)
        - Immigration, 1990 (Box 185, Folder 19)
        - La Condonera, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 20)
        - Latina/o Hour, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 21)
        - Latinos and AIDS information, 1990 (Box 185, Folder 22)
        - Latino issues and dating, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 23)
        - Latino programs, 1989-1991 (Box 185, Folder 24)
        - Latinos Unidos Contra el SIDA, LUCES (Box 185, Folder 25)
        - People of Color Resource Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 186, Folder 1)
        - Program development, 1991 (Box 186, Folder 2)
        - Puerto Rican Day Parade, 1991 (Box 186, Folder 3)
        - Service Provider Focus Group for Those Who Work with Latino Men with HIV in New York City, 1997 (Box 186, Folder 4)
        - SIDAhora Magazine, 1991 (Box 186, Folder 5)
        - Spanish Language Work Group, 1991 (Box 186, Folder 6)
        - What's in it 4 Me?, 1991-1992 (Box 186, Folder 7-8)
        - Youth Work Group, 1991 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - VII. D. 7. Speakers Bureau, 1984-1988
      - General, 1986 (Box 186, Folder 10)